export const QuizData = [
  //Lesson 1

  {
    questionText: "右",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'sun', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'moon', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'right', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'left', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "円",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'sun', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'yen', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'king', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'noise', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },

  {
    questionText: "花",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'flower', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'down', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'science', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'fire', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  
  {
    questionText: "音",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'school', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'sound', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'spirit', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'left', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "気",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'circle', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'down', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'spirit', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'rain', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "休",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'ball', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'gold', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'rest', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'nine', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "空",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'sun', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'sky', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'spirit', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'noise', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },

  {
    questionText: "犬",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'cat', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'cow', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'rat', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'dog', isCorrect: true },
    ],
  },

  {
    questionText: "口",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'sun', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'moon', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'mouth', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'eye', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "月",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'circle', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'month', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'year', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'rain', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "校",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'school', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'gold', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'left', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'right', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "山",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'sun', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'mountain', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'child', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'noise', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "糸",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'letter', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'ear', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'thread', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'dog', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "車",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'hand', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'child', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'mouth', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'car', isCorrect: true },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "手",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'hand', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'month', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'mouth', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'year', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "女",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'woman', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'man', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'left', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'right', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "小",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'up', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'small', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'down', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'child', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "森",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'letter', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'forest', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'person', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'dog', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "水",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'water', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'person', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'life', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'car', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionText: "青",
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'hand', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'blue', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'red', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'mouth', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
 


 



  
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "赤",
    choices: ["blue", "red", "left", "right"],
    answer: "red",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "先",
    choices: ["up", "before", "down", "river"],
    answer: "before",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "川",
    choices: ["dog", "forest", "person", "river"],
    answer: "river",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "草",
    choices: ["water", "grass", "forest", "river"],
    answer: "grass",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "村",
    choices: ["village", "mouth", "leg", "bamboo"],
    answer: "village",
  },

  //Lesson 6
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "町",
    choices: ["village", "town", "left", "right"],
    answer: "town",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "天",
    choices: ["up", "spirit", "down", "sky"],
    answer: "sky",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "日",
    choices: ["day", "moon", "insect", "river"],
    answer: "day",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "年",
    choices: ["sun", "month", "year", "river"],
    answer: "year",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "田",
    choices: ["village", "rice field", "town", "bamboo"],
    answer: "village",
  },
  //Lesson 7
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "白",
    choices: ["white", "red", "blue", "black"],
    answer: "white",
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "文",
    choices: ["word", "sentence", "down", "up"],
    answer: "sentence",
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "本",
    choices: ["tree", "book", "person", "dog"],
    answer: "book",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "名",
    choices: ["name", "month", "year", "person"],
    answer: "year",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "目",
    choices: ["hand", "eye", "foot", "mouth"],
    answer: "eye",
  },
  //Lesson 8
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "豉",
    choices: ["park", "beans", "far", "black"],
    answer: "beans",
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "黄",
    choices: ["white", "yellow", "red", "green"],
    answer: "yellow",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "何",
    choices: ["tree", "house", "what", "meeting"],
    answer: "what",
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "会",
    choices: ["meeting", "month", "year", "park"],
    answer: "meeting",
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "力",
    choices: ["hand", "power", "tree", "water"],
    answer: "power",
  },
];
